Iván Gajate Pascua

Front-end developer

Iván Gajate Pascua

Villanúa, Huesca (Spain)

(+34) 620 32 55 20 ivangajate@gmail.com www.yporqueno.es



Skills

I'm passionate about development and web technologies. I have worked in this area for more than fifteen years, deploying interactive CDs, Flash microsites, and complex apps built in JavaScript. Now totally focused into Web Components development with Lit Elements.

I would like to use all this experience to provide a global and more human vision to the projects .

Experience

Roche, Web Components developer using Lit

January 2021 - Currently

Web Components development for the Roche Design System, in order to be consumed by each project development team. Using JavaScript native closest technologies.

I always develop with good-practices in mind. Clean-code, deep unit test and integration test, always looking for 100% coverage. SonarQube for checking the quality of the code passed at 100% too.

I am passionate about pair-programming, even eXtreme-programming as the only way of product development.

Through NextLink Group.

BBVA in several teams, Front-end developer

September 2019 - January 2021

Development of the BBVA global app. Polymer and LitElement technologies through GFT IT Consulting.

Ticksy app, co-founder and developer

2019 - Currently

Ticksy is an app to manage bars and restaurants. Development of the app admin dashboard.

The front-end app dashboard is developed with the VueJs framework and the back-end with Google Firebase technology.

Trainer and speaker in talks about web development

2003 - Currently

Talks about JavaScript technology, VueJs, Design Patterns, Object-Oriented Programming, Functional programming, Firebase...

Web apps developer, Front-end developer

2015 - 2019

Web apps developer, Single Page Applications with VueJs

Fullsix Madrid, Head of Creative Technologies

2013 - 2015

Head of the front-end development team. A 7 people team composed of web designers, developers, and analysts.

Uve Agency, Creative developer

2008 - 2013

Interactive web sites development with Flash, HTML and JavaScript.

Netthink Carat (Isobar), Head of Front-end development team

2005 - 2008

Development of Flash advertising microsites, with ActionScript complex code.

Advertising formats with high visual impact.

Several advertising agencies and producers, multimedia developer

2002 - 2005

Multimedia CD developer, in Macromedia Director and Flash.

Education

Time management course.

2016

JavaScript for professionals.

2013

Adobe Certified Associate

2011

Design and Multimedia Development Master

2001 - 2003

Industrial technical engineering (EUITI, Madrid, Spain)

1999 - 2001

Languages

English B2.